var QandA = [
    {
        question: "What year was George R.R. Martin's book 'A Game of Thrones' published?",
        answers: ["1989", "2003", "1996", "2005"],
        rightAnswer: 2
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of Jon Snow's direwolf?",
        answers: ["Lady", "Ghost", "Grey Wind", "Wolf"],
        rightAnswer: 1
    }, {
        question: "At whose castle did the 'Red Wedding' take place?",
        answers: ["Winterfell", "Dragonstone", "Casterly Rock", "Riverrun"],
        rightAnswer: 3
    }, {
        question: "Which dragon did Daenerys ride most frequently?",
        answers: ["Drogon", "Rhaegal", "Viserion", "Aegon"],
        rightAnswer: 0
    }, {
        question: "At the beginning of the series, how many children do Ned and Catelyn Stark have?",
        answers: ["Four", "Five", "Three", "Six"],
        rightAnswer: 1
    }, {
        question: "Who kills the Night King?",
        answers: ["Jon Snow", "Daenerys Targaryen", "Arya Stark", "Bran Stark"],
        rightAnswer: 2
    }, {
        question: "Who creates a special saddle for the paralyzed Bran to ride a horse again?",
        answers: ["Tyrion Lannister", "Robb Stark", "Jon Snow", "Ned Stark"],
        rightAnswer: 0
    }, {
        question: "Who is the youngest of the Stark siblings?",
        answers: ["Rickon", "Arya", "Bran", "Sansa"],
        rightAnswer: 0
    }, {
        question: "What is the name of Brienne of Tarth's sword?",
        answers: ["Baratheon", "Oathkeeper", "Longclaw", "A sword has no name"],
        rightAnswer: 1
    }, {
        question: "Who was Arya Stark's sword master?",
        answers: ["Jaqen H'ghar", "Sandor Clegane", "Eddard Stark", "Syrio Forel"],
        rightAnswer: 3
    }
];

console.log(QandA);